YouTube Present Award to Emmanuel TV
Congratulations, Emmanuel TV family!
Congratulations, viewers all over the world!
Emmanuel TV has received an award from one of the most popular globally engaging,
reputable and objective websites which cuts across nationalities, race and class.
Think about it. What website could that be?
YouTube!
Yes, Emmanuel TV has received this award from YouTube.
Emmanuel
His name is called Emmanuel
For surpassing the milestone of 100,000 subscribers on our YouTube channel Emmanuel TV.
And this is the accompanying letter.
Let's read it.
From YouTube:
You've just done something very few YouTube creators accomplish:
You had an astonishing 100,000 people subscribe to your channel.
We know numbers on YouTube can get really big,
but we hope you don't lose sight of the reality behind that six-digit milestone.
Each and every person who has subscribed to your channel was touched by what you did.
They were inspired or challenged or entertained.
You made it to this milestone with hard work, perseverance,
and - chances are - a healthy sense of humor.
What you've accomplished can't be taken away from you.
And we'd like to recognize you and all your hard work with this silver play button,
a small token of our esteem and respect.
We know you don't do this for rewards.
You do it because you have a drive to create and share,
and because you've found an audience who cares.
Believe us when we say that we can't wait to see what you do next.
A million subscribers may seem a long way off right now, but you're closer than you think
And we're rooting for you.
Congratulations. Sincerely, the CEO of YouTube.
Viewers, thank you!
You can see how YouTube appreciates you.
Now how did this award come about?
YouTube has grown to become one of the world's most recognizable websites
with over a billion users, almost one-third of all people on the internet.
It is a website that embraces good things in humanity and wants to reach out to viewers all over the world
with what they want to know and what will benefit them.
This is what makes YouTube different.
Now let's get back to Emmanuel TV.
Our YouTube channel was launched on December 10, 2012.
It has amassed over 200 million views since its inception,
to become the world's most viewed Christian ministry YouTube channel of all time.
Whether it's touching the screen and praying along with Prophet T.B. Joshua,
feeding on the word of God through powerful sermons,
learning from real-life experiences and life-changing testimonies,
seeing the evidence of Jesus in action,
reaching out to a troubled world through humanitarian projects worldwide,
witnessing the undeniable confirmations of prophecy -
personal, national and international -
or tuning in to experience the power of God in the Sunday live broadcast.
Emmanuel TV is one with a difference.
And viewers, it is all because of you.
You have made all this possible because you view our channel Emmanuel TV.
I am because you are, you are because I am.
Thank you for your support.
This is a relationship - Christianity is a relationship.
Now let's take a look at where and how you watch Emmanuel TV
that has made us the world's most viewed Christian ministry YouTube channel ever.
Emmanuel TV English YouTube channel: total views - over 200 million,
total watch time - over 1.5 billion minutes watched,
subscribers - over half a million,
top countries: one - United States,
two - United Kingdom, three - South Africa, four - Nigeria, five - Canada.
Emmanuel TV Spanish YouTube channel: total views - over 45 million,
total watch time - over 300 million minutes watched,
subscribers - over 120,000,
top countries: one - Mexico. two - United States, three - Colombia,
four - Argentina, five - Peru.
Emmanuel TV Portuguese YouTube channel: total views - over six million,
total watch time - over 25 million minutes watched,
subscribers - over 24,000,
top countries: one - Brazil, two - Angola,
three - Portugal, four - Mozambique, five - United States.
And our growing French channel.
Emmanuel TV French YouTube channel: total views - over 150,000,
total watch time - over 1 million minutes watched,
subscribers - over 3,000,
top countries: one - France, two - French Guiana, three - Canada,
four - Belgium, five - Germany.
Total minutes watched of all Emmanuel TV YouTube channels - over two billion minutes.
So, viewers, thank you for making history.
Together we are changing lives, changing nations and the world.
Every day, we receive countless emails, messages and videos of people
who have been touched, healed, blessed and delivered through watching Emmanuel TV.
When you give your attention to God, you are what God says you are,
you have what God says you have
and you can do what God says you can do.
As you give your seconds, minutes, hours to God through watching Emmanuel TV online,
on your phone, tablet, laptop, computer or TV,
you are connected to the Maker of Heaven and earth
who is busy right now, changing your story.
Thank you for spending your time with us.
You can upload your testimony to i.emmanuel.tv.
And you can also watch the SCOAN Live Sunday Service on our website
or stream live on YouTube, Facebook or Periscope.
Remember, the founder, the inspiration, the motivation of Emmanuel TV is Jesus Christ
and as Prophet T.B. Joshua always says,
"For those whose lives are centered in Christ Jesus, the best is always yet to come".
This is Emmanuel TV! God With Us!